<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Robin Hensel | Indian Land Republican Women</title>
    <link>/authors/robin-hensel/</link>
      <atom:link href="/authors/robin-hensel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Robin Hensel</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Indian Land Republican Women &amp;nbsp; © 2019</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 13:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Robin Hensel</title>
      <link>/authors/robin-hensel/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian Land Republican Women Minutes</title>
      <link>/talk/august-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/august-2018/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;minutes&#34;&gt;Minutes&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Indian Land Republican Women club met for the official charter meeting at Midtown Sundries on Thursday, August
9th. President, Michelle Simonetti called the meeting to order at 7:05pm. Vice President Anita Joye led with invocation
then Vice President Beverly Williams led with the Pledge of Allegiance. Former Clover/Lake Wylie Republican Women
Club President Peggy Upchurch presented the Republican pin to Michelle Simonetti. President, Clover-Lake Wylie
Republican Women, Rozalynn Federline presented funds to begin the club from the Lancaster republican women club
that dissolved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Introductions of new associate members: Brandon Newton, Brian Carnes, Earl Capps, Melvin Stroble
Guest Speaker Lancaster County School District 1, YMCA Board Member, Indian Land Christmas Parade Director
Melvin Stroble gave his speech “It is up to us!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Old business: Motion to confirm temporary board as President Michelle Simonetti, 1st VP Anita Joye, 2nd VP Beverly
Williams, 3rd VP Libby Venditti, Treasurer Nancy Connor. Motion for Margaret Devincenti as Secretary was made by
Robin Hensel and second by Beverly Williams. Other leadership roles in committees open. Dues accepted and passed
as $35 voting members ($15 going to federation), $10 associate members. Meetings will be held 2nd Thursday each
month excluding summers and only required six meetings per year. Bylaws were motioned and 2nd to be submitted.
Announcement: Americans for Prosperity meeting tonight at Hickory Tavern&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New business: Raffle for Trump wine winner was Earl Capps who passed gift to rightful woman Beverly Williams.
Hillary Clinton TP prize awarded to Libby Venditti.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Members were reminded that the next ILRW meeting will be on Thursday, September 13th at 7:00 PM. Guest speakers
will be November candidates Dee Studebaker, Brandon Newton and presentation on recreation bond. Meeting was
adjourned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Respectfully submitted by Robin Hensel&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
