<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meeting Minutes | Indian Land Republican Women</title>
    <link>/talk/</link>
      <atom:link href="/talk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Meeting Minutes</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Indian Land Republican Women &amp;nbsp; © 2019</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 13:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Meeting Minutes</title>
      <link>/talk/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian Land Republican Women Minutes</title>
      <link>/talk/september-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/september-2018/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;minutes&#34;&gt;Minutes&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Indian Land Republican Women club met for our second official charter meeting at Midtown Sundries on Thursday,
September 13th. President, Michelle Simonetti called the meeting to order at 7:07pm. Claire McConaughay led with invocation
then Vice President Beverly Williams led with the Pledge of Allegiance. Nancy Connor gave a treasurer report balance of
$339.64, some funds were used for office supplies and renting a booth at the Fall Festival. Change in secretary was announced,
Giovanna Aspesi will be the new secretary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Introductions of all present began. Attendees found out about meeting from friends, Gateway Ad and Facebook. Our goal is to
network in the community and get some female republican candidates.
Announcement: We will need volunteers for our Fall Festival booth. A sign up sheet was passed around.
New Business: Guest Speakers tonight will be Candidate Probate Judge Dee Studebaker, House Representative Brandon
Newton, Lauren Thomas “Be in Favor” about the upcoming Rec Bond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dee Studebaker is running for a four year term of Probate Judge. She is Lancaster County Associate Probate Judge. She is an
attorney with 24 years of experience. She lives in Indian Land with her husband and two sons. She explained to us that a
probate judge deals with estates, guardianship of children, as well as, mental illness detention orders. She asked for our support
in November.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brandon Newton is our current District 45 House Representative and is running for re-election. He discussed
some accomplishments from this last session: HOA reform, more money for education and roads. Hoping to work on pension
reform next.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lauren Thomas spoke to us about the upcoming rec bond. The county is currently spending $13 per person on recreation. We
have around 93,000 people in the Lancaster area. Compared to other areas this is very low. Bond would allow for updates to be
made at the Indian Land recreation center, development of land on Harrisburg Road into 2 fields with artificial turf and
parking/concession area. Kershaw/Health Springs will get a field with artificial turf and Lindsey Pettus Greenway Auditorium will
be updated. If bond is passed cost to taxpayers will be $16 per 100,000 of home value. Maintenance cost would have to be
covered by county.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Members were reminded that the next ILRW meeting will be on Monday October 8th at 7:00 PM, not Oct 11th as Sun City
Republican club will be joining us to host November candidates. Location is Rebound Behavioral Health 134 E Rebound Rd,
Lancaster SC. Guest speakers will be Congressman Ralph Norman, Attorney General Alan Wilson, County School Board
candidates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meeting was adjourned at 8:27pm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Respectfully submitted by Giovanna Aspesi&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian Land Republican Women Minutes</title>
      <link>/talk/august-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/august-2018/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;minutes&#34;&gt;Minutes&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Indian Land Republican Women club met for the official charter meeting at Midtown Sundries on Thursday, August
9th. President, Michelle Simonetti called the meeting to order at 7:05pm. Vice President Anita Joye led with invocation
then Vice President Beverly Williams led with the Pledge of Allegiance. Former Clover/Lake Wylie Republican Women
Club President Peggy Upchurch presented the Republican pin to Michelle Simonetti. President, Clover-Lake Wylie
Republican Women, Rozalynn Federline presented funds to begin the club from the Lancaster republican women club
that dissolved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Introductions of new associate members: Brandon Newton, Brian Carnes, Earl Capps, Melvin Stroble
Guest Speaker Lancaster County School District 1, YMCA Board Member, Indian Land Christmas Parade Director
Melvin Stroble gave his speech “It is up to us!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Old business: Motion to confirm temporary board as President Michelle Simonetti, 1st VP Anita Joye, 2nd VP Beverly
Williams, 3rd VP Libby Venditti, Treasurer Nancy Connor. Motion for Margaret Devincenti as Secretary was made by
Robin Hensel and second by Beverly Williams. Other leadership roles in committees open. Dues accepted and passed
as $35 voting members ($15 going to federation), $10 associate members. Meetings will be held 2nd Thursday each
month excluding summers and only required six meetings per year. Bylaws were motioned and 2nd to be submitted.
Announcement: Americans for Prosperity meeting tonight at Hickory Tavern&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New business: Raffle for Trump wine winner was Earl Capps who passed gift to rightful woman Beverly Williams.
Hillary Clinton TP prize awarded to Libby Venditti.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Members were reminded that the next ILRW meeting will be on Thursday, September 13th at 7:00 PM. Guest speakers
will be November candidates Dee Studebaker, Brandon Newton and presentation on recreation bond. Meeting was
adjourned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Respectfully submitted by Robin Hensel&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
